<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="fish">
        <item>Carp</item>
        <item>Pike</item>
        <item>Catfish</item>
        <item>Burbot</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="fish_content">
        <item>
            various species of oily freshwater fish from the family Cyprinidae,
            a very large group of fish native to Europe and Asia.
            While carp is consumed in many parts of the world, they are
            generally considered an invasive species in parts of Africa,
            Australia and most of the United States.
        </item>
        <item>species of carnivorous fish of the genus Esox (the pikes).
            They are typical of brackish and fresh waters of the Northern
            Hemisphere (i.e. holarctic in distribution). They are known simply
            as a pike in Britain, Ireland, and most of Eastern Europe, Canada
            and the United States.
        </item>
        <item>
            diverse group of ray-finned fish. Named for their prominent barbels,
            which resemble a cat whiskers, catfish range in size and behavior from
            the three largest species alive, the Mekong giant catfish from Southeast
            Asia, the wels catfish of Eurasia, and the piraiba of South America, to
            detritivores (species that eat dead material on the bottom), and even to
            a tiny parasitic species commonly called the candiru, Vandellia cirrhosa.
        </item>
        <item>
            only gadiform (cod-like) freshwater fish. It is also known as bubbot,
            mariah, freshwater cod, freshwater ling, freshwater cusk, the lawyer,
            coney-fish, lingcod, and eelpout. The species is closely related to the
            marine common ling and the cusk. It is the only member of the genus Lota.
            For some time of the year, the burbot lives under ice, and it requires
            frigid temperatures to breed.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="fish_image_array">
        <item>@drawable/crusian_carp</item>
        <item>@drawable/pike</item>
        <item>@drawable/catfish</item>
        <item>@drawable/burbot</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="na">
        <item>Carp bait</item>
        <item>Pike bait</item>
        <item>Catfish bait</item>
        <item>Burbot bait</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="na_content">
        <item>
            A common worm ...
            Maggot for fishing ...
            Bark beetle larva ...
            Dragonfly for fishing ...
            Canned corn ...
            Green pea ...
            Boiled potatoes for fishing ...
            Wheat or pearl barley
        </item>
        <item>
            bleak;
            roach;
            carp;
            perch;
            ruff;
            gudgeon and other medium-sized fish.
        </item>
        <item>
            Crawling out.
            Zhivets.
            Frog.
            Sparrow.
            Perlovitsa.
            Locusts.
            Chicken liver.
            Pieces of fish.
        </item>
        <item>
            bunches of red worms,
            chicken offal,
            crawling,
            leeches,
            fish
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="na_image_array">
        <item>@drawable/crusian_carp</item>
        <item>@drawable/pike</item>
        <item>@drawable/catfish</item>
        <item>@drawable/burbot</item>
    </array>
</resources>